Oversize
Marist College
Oversize
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.2.12
1203 Linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
Glass plate negatives
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Materials, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass plate negatives, 2.1.1
        - Lowell Thomas, 2.1.1.2
          - Oversize, 2.1.1.2.12
              - Ancestors [split glass plate negative], undated; 1 (Box 1330)
                8x10
              - Ancestors [split glass plate negative], undated; 2
              - Ancestors [split glass plate negative], undated; 3
              - Isaac’s Tomb, Abraham’s Tomb, Mayor of Jerusalem and two British soldiers at surrender of Jerusalem [split glass plate negative], 1918; 4
                6.5x8.5
              - View from airplane of Port Said (aerial view), Sudan sandstorm [split glass plate negative], 1918; 5
              - Lowell Thomas and T. E. Lawrence standing in front of tent, 1918; 6
              - Lowell Thomas with motion picture camera in airplane before taking off for a flight from Egypt to Jerusalem, 1918; 7
              - Two airplanes in clouds, one plane in cloud, squadron on ground, 1918; 8
              - Linton Wells (copy made for Lowell Thomas), 7/1/1925; 9
              - Map of Near East, Petra indicated with bright red star, 1920; 10
              - Auda Abu Tayi, center, and two brothers, 1918; 11